Bob Bullock Comptroller of Public Accounts papers, Inclusive: 1970-1991, Bulk: 1975-1990
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
- Reports, 1978-1990; 6
  - Questionnaires: K. Dressler (4 of 6), 1984 (Box 333, Folder 4)
  - Questionnaires: K. Dressler (5 of 6), 1984 (Box 333, Folder 5)
  - Questionnaires: K. Dressler (6 of 6), 1984 (Box 333, Folder 6)
  - Reproduction Division (1 of 2), 1979-1982 (Box 333, Folder 7)
  - Reproduction Division (2 of 2), 1979-1982 (Box 333, Folder 8)
  - Rethinking Texas Taxes, Vol. I & II (1 of 8), 1989 January (Box 334, Folder 1)
  - Rethinking Texas Taxes, Vol. I & II (2 of 8), 1989 January (Box 334, Folder 2)
  - Rethinking Texas Taxes, Vol. I & II (3 of 8), 1989 January (Box 334, Folder 3)
  - Rethinking Texas Taxes, Vol. I & II (4 of 8), 1989 January (Box 334, Folder 4)
  - Rethinking Texas Taxes, Vol. I & II (5 of 8), 1989 January (Box 334, Folder 5)
  - Rethinking Texas Taxes, Vol. I & II (6 of 8), 1989 January (Box 334, Folder 6)
  - Rethinking Texas Taxes, Vol. I & II (7 of 8), 1989 January (Box 334, Folder 7)
  - Rethinking Texas Taxes, Vol. I & II (8 of 8), 1989 January (Box 334, Folder 8)
  - “Review of Agency Activities”, 1984 (Box 334, Folder 9)
  - Salaries and Budgets (1 of 3), 1976-1983 (Box 334, Folder 10)
  - Salaries and Budgets (2 of 3), 1976-1983 (Box 334, Folder 11)
  - Salaries and Budgets (3 of 3), 1976-1983 (Box 334, Folder 12)
  - Special Financial Reports, 1983-1990 (Box 335, Folder 1)
  - Special Operations (1 of 2), 1979-1982 (Box 335, Folder 2)
  - Special Operations (2 of 2), 1979-1982 (Box 335, Folder 3)
  - Speeches: on Behalf of Bob Bullock (1 of 5), 1982-1983 (Box 335, Folder 4)
  - Speeches: on Behalf of Bob Bullock (2 of 5), 1982-1983 (Box 335, Folder 5)
  - Speeches: on Behalf of Bob Bullock (3 of 5), 1982-1983 (Box 335, Folder 6)
  - Speeches: on Behalf of Bob Bullock (4 of 5), 1982-1983 (Box 335, Folder 7)
  - Speeches: on Behalf of Bob Bullock (5 of 5), 1982-1983 (Box 335, Folder 8)
  - “State of Texas Comptrollers, 1835-1975” Evaluation & Statistics Division, 1982 January (Box 335, Folder 9)
  - “State Revenue AlternativesEL”, 1985 (Box 335, Folder 10)
  - Statistical Information, 1975-1982 (Box 335, Folder 11)
  - Subcommittees (1 of 7), 1984 (Box 336, Folder 1)
  - Subcommittees (2 of 7), 1984 (Box 336, Folder 2)
  - Subcommittees (3 of 7), 1984 (Box 336, Folder 3)
  - Subcommittees (4 of 7), 1984 (Box 336, Folder 4)
  - Subcommittees (5 of 7), 1984 (Box 336, Folder 5)
  - Subcommittees (6 of 7), 1984 (Box 336, Folder 6)
  - Subcommittees (7 of 7), 1984 (Box 336, Folder 7)
  - “Summary of EnactmentsEL”, 1985 (Box 336, Folder 8)
  - Task Force: Comptroller’s Office: Penalty and Interest Waiver Policy, Part I, 1982 (Box 336, Folder 9)
  - Task Force: Comptroller’s Office: Timely Filing Policy, Part II, 1982 (Box 336, Folder 10)
  - Task Force: Comptroller’s Office: Merit and Reclassification Policy, Part III, 1982 (Box 336, Folder 11)
  - Task Force: Comptroller’s Office: Placing Terminals in Other Agencies for Vendor Inquiry, Part IV, 1982 (Box 336, Folder 12)
  - Task Force: Comptroller’s Office: Agency Mailout Policy, Part V, 1982 (Box 336, Folder 13)
  - Task Force: Comptroller’s Office: Report on Recommendations to Mr. Bullock from Field Managers and Division Directors, Part VI, 1982 (Box 336, Folder 14)
  - Tax Information Division: Weekly Reports, undated (Box 337, Folder 1)
  - Testimony on Education, 1974-1978 (Box 337, Folder 2)
  - “Texas and TaxesEL”, undated (Box 337, Folder 3)
  - “Texas Department of Housing and Community Affairs”, 1998 (Box 337, Folder 4)
  - “Texas Facts: Background Information on Texas’s Taxes and SpendingEL” (1 of 2), 1986 (Box 337, Folder 5)
  - “Texas Facts: Background Information on Texas’s Taxes and SpendingEL” (2 of 2), 1986 (Box 337, Folder 6)
  - “Texas First”, 1985 (Box 337, Folder 7)
  - “Texas InventoryEL”, 1985-1986 (Box 337, Folder 8)
  - “Texas Inventory: An Analysis of Texas”, undated (Box 337, Folder 9)
  - “Texas State Finances and the Texas Economic Outlook” (1 of 2), 1986 (Box 337, Folder 10)
  - “Texas State Finances and the Texas Economic Outlook” (2 of 2), 1986 (Box 337, Folder 11)
  - Training Division Evaluation and Recommendations, 1985 (Box 337, Folder 12)
  - Warrants Held Due to Delinquent Student Loans, 1979 (Box 337, Folder 13)
  - Weekly Status Reports (1 of 4), 1984-1985 (Box 337, Folder 14)
  - Weekly Status Reports (2 of 4), 1984-1985 (Box 337, Folder 15)
  - Weekly Status Reports (3 of 4), 1984-1985 (Box 337, Folder 16)
  - Weekly Status Reports (4 of 4), 1984-1985 (Box 337, Folder 17)
- Publications, 1986-1990; 7
  This series contains publications such as The Capital Griddle and other newsletters.
  - Other: Miscellaneous: The Capital Griddle, 1986-1989 (Box 338, Folder 1)
  - Newsletters: "Texas Agenda", 1989 April (Box 338, Folder 2)
  - Newsletters: "The Texas Prosecutor", 1990 May-June (Box 338, Folder 3)
  - Newsletters: "Quorum Report", 1989 (Box 338, Folder 4)
  - Newsletters: "Quorum Report", 1989 (Box 338, Folder 5)
  - Newsletters, undated (Box 338, Folder 6)